codespeedy.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy - CodeSpeedy

This page informs about our policies regarding the use, collection, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service or our website www.codespeedy.com and your choices that are associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

## Information Collection And Use

We collect several types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service for you.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited. These are email address, name, phone number, address. During browsing our website we may store cookies and usage data.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect Usage Data that may include information like your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

## Disclosure Of Data

### Legal Requirements

CodeSpeedy may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of CodeSpeedy
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and any websites can be attacked any time and steal the data. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites and these are not operated by us. If you click on a third party website or link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Some of the links are the links are redirected to third party and most of them are affiliate link. Using those affiliate links will not cost any extra money from the users or visitors of our website
